Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - A
        - Ambassadors of Funk - Supermarioland, 1992; SR-10644; Ambassadors of Funk; MC Mario (Box 170)
          Catalog # SMASH 23; A-side Matrix # SMASH 23 A2
          Living Beat Records
          England
        - Ambassadors of Funk - My minds made up, 1988; SR-10645; Ambassadors of Funk (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10646. 2 copies
          Catalog # BCM 12018; A-side Matrix # BC 12018-A
          BCM Records
        - Ambassadors of Funk - My minds made up, 1988; SR-10646; Ambassadors of Funk (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10645. 2 copies
        - Amber - Sexual (li da di), 1999; SR-10647; Amber (Box 170)
          Catalog # TB381A; A-side Matrix # TB381-A
        - Amber - Colour of love, 1996; SR-10648; Amber (Box 170)
          Catalog # TB748A; A-side Matrix # TB-748A
        - Ambersunshower - Walter T; Beautiful, 1996; SR-10649; Ambersunshower (Box 170)
          Catalog # PR12 7257-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-7257-1-AS/SP1
          Gee Street
        - Ambitious Lovers - Love overlap, 1988; SR-10650; Ambitious Lovers (Box 170)
          Catalog # DMD 1195; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-55274-1
        - America's Most Wanted - Wash out ya beever; America's most wanted, 1990; SR-10651; America's Most Wanted (Box 170)
          Catalog # GR-100; A-side Matrix # GRC-100-A
          Gangster Records
        - American Fade - I'm alive (let's move on), 1983; SR-10652; American Fade (Box 170)
          Catalog # DS420A; A-side Matrix # DS-420-A
          Dance-Sing Records
          Farmingdale, New York
        - American Space Travelers - Rock & roll (this is jungle sky volume 5), 1998; SR-10653; American Space Travelers (Box 170)
          Catalog # JS128; A-side Matrix # JS128A
          Jungle Sky
        - American Steel - Shake your body line, 1986; SR-10654; American Steel (Box 170)
          Catalog # 3001; A-side Matrix # 3001-A
          Lulu Records
        - AMG - Bitch betta have my money, 1991; SR-10657; AMG (Box 170)
          Catalog # 1-21642; A-side Matrix # SEL-21642-1-A DMM-1
        - AMG - Bitch betta have my money, 1991; SR-10658; AMG (Box 170)
          Catalog # FMS 62377; A-side Matrix # FMS-62377A
        - AMG - Pimp of the century, 1995; SR-10659; AMG (Box 170)
          Catalog # PRO-49; A-side Matrix # PRO-49-A
        - AMG - Around the world, 1995; SR-10660; AMG (Box 171)
          Catalog # 25042-1; A-side Matrix # 1-25042-A
        - Amigos - Cheek to cheek; Pegaito, 1987; SR-10661; Amigos; Bad Street Boys (Box 171)
          Catalog # JAP-525; A-side Matrix # JAP 525-A1
          JAP Records
        - Amil - For da fam, 2000; SR-10662; Amil; Beanie Siegel; Memphis Bleek Jay-Z (Box 171)
          Catalog # CAS 12852; A-side Matrix # XSS-12852A-1B
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - Amina - Belly dance, 1990; SR-10663; Amina (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10664. Different discs
          Catalog # 537 845-1; A-side Matrix # 162 537 845-1-A-SP
          Mango Records
        - Amina - Belly dance, 1989; SR-10664; Amina (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10663. Different discs
          Catalog # 874 433-1; A-side Matrix # 874433-1 A
          Philips
        - Amina - Belly dance, 1989; SR-10665; Amina (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10666. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # 874 433-1; A-side Matrix # 874433-1A
        - Amina - Belly dance, 1989; SR-10666; Amina (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10665. 2 copies
        - Amina - Belly dance, 1989; SR-10667; Amina (Box 171)
        - Amina - Yalil, 1989; SR-10668; Amina (Box 171)
          Catalog # 838 609-1; A-side Matrix # 838609-1A
        - Amina - My desire, 1997; SR-10669; Amina (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10670. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # VCRT27; A-side Matrix # VCRT 27 A-1-1
          VC Recordings
        - Amina - My desire, 1997; SR-10670; Amina (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10669. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Amina - My desire, 1997; SR-10671; Amina (Box 171)
          Catalog # VCRTDJ27; A-side Matrix # VCRTDJ 27 A-1-1
        - Amoretto - Cláve rocks, 1986; SR-10672; Amoretto (Box 171)
          Catalog # KO-003; A-side Matrix # K003-A
          PKO Recordings
        - Amorin, Jo - Joy and love, 1986; SR-10673; Amorin, Jo (Box 171)
          Catalog # IAP 060456; A-side Matrix # 060456 A
          International Amorin's Production
        - A.M.P. - Seventh sign...; Today yesterday, 2002; SR-10674; A.M.P. (Box 171)
          Catalog # BOP001; A-side Matrix # BOPR-001-A
          Bank of Portugal Records
          Canada
        - A.M.P. - Seventh sign...; Today yesterday, 2002; SR-10675; A.M.P. (Box 171)
        - A.M.P. - AMP army, 2004; SR-10676; A.M.P. (Box 171)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # AMP V-A
        - Amra - Dancin, 1983; SR-10677; Amra (Box 171)
          Catalog # FUNK-007; A-side Matrix # F.007.A
          T.C.I. Productions
        - Amuzement Park - Groove your blues away, 1982; SR-10678; Amuzement Park (Box 171)
          Catalog # OG 12 901; A-side Matrix # OG-12901 006121214-A-1-1-1
          Our Gang Entertainment
          Cleveland, Ohio
        - Amyth - 1,2,3; Who shot your heart?, 1999; SR-10679; Amyth (Box 171)
          Catalog # PRO-A-9814; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9814-A-SRI
        - Anches Doo Too Cool - C'est quoi l'histoire ?!, 1987; SR-10680; Anches Doo Too Cool (Box 171)
          Catalog # ATT 56; A-side Matrix # ATT 56 A
          Attitude
        - Anderson, Carl - Don't make me wait, 1984; SR-10681; Anderson, Carl (Box 171)
          Catalog # 49-05036; A-side Matrix # XSS-171822-1A
        - Anderson, Paula - Four year battle, 1984; SR-10682; Anderson, Paula (Box 171)
          Catalog # DMD 811; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-47357-1
        - Anderson, Sunshine - Heard it all before (Dance Remixes), 2001; SR-10683; Anderson, Sunshine; E-Smoove; Watt, Ben (Box 171)
          Catalog # PR 300572; A-side Matrix # STDM-90219-90220-1
        - Atahualpa 1530 - Andino, 1990; SR-10684; Atahualpa 1530 (Box 171)
          Catalog # DFC 024; A-side Matrix # DCF024-AA
          DCF
          Bologna, Italy
        - Andrew K - Endlessly, 1995; SR-10685; Andrew K (Box 171)
          Catalog # MRCVIP 1064; A-side Matrix # MRCVIP-1046-A
          Viper Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Andrews Sisters - Boogie woogie bugle girls, 1973; SR-10686; Andrews Sisters (Box 171)
          Catalog # PA 6075; A-side Matrix # PA-6075-A
          Paramount Records
        - Angel, Luis - Dicen que dicen; Un amor como el mio, 1986; SR-10687; Angel, Luis (Box 171)
          Catalog # SP-17427; A-side Matrix # AMSP017427-A RCA2
          A y M Discos
          Mexico
        - Angel Heart - Come on let's work, 1995; SR-10688; Angel Heart (Box 171)
          Catalog # DOS OR DIE 016; A-side Matrix # DOS 016-A1
        - Angela - Bebe; Shame, 2001; SR-10689; Angela (Box 171)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # 08 46479 20 1A1 NEO 2001
          Make It Sound
        - Angie B. - It's my life, 1995; SR-10690; Angie B. (Box 171)
          Catalog # 75270-74001-1; A-side Matrix # 75270-74001-1-A
          Bust It Records
          Oakland, California
        - Angie B. - It's my life, 1995; SR-10691; Angie B. (Box 171)
          Catalog # 75270-74001-1; A-side Matrix # 75270-75001-1-A
        - Anggun - Snow on the Sahara, 1997; SR-10692; Anggun (Box 171)
          Catalog # EAS 41597; A-side Matrix # XSS-41597-A
        - Animal Nightlife - Love is just the great pretender, 1982; SR-10693; Animal Nightlife (Box 171)
          Catalog # IVL A 13 2881; A-side Matrix # IVL A 13 2881 A 1
          Inner Vision Records
        - Animotion - I engineer (Remix), 1986; SR-10694; Animotion (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10695. 2 copies
          Catalog # 884 433-1; A-side Matrix # 884-433-1-85-CS 807 ES
          Casablanca
        - Animotion - I engineer (Remix), 1986; SR-10695; Animotion (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10694. 2 copies
        - Anka, Paul - Gimme the word, 1983; SR-10696; Anka, Paul (Box 171)
          Catalog # 44-04240; A-side Matrix # XSS169512-1A
        - A.N.M. - Muevete, 1997; SR-10780; A.N.M. (Box 171)
          Catalog # DFC 1301; A-side Matrix # DFC-1301-A
          DFC
        - Annett - Walk like a man, 1985; SR-10697; Annett (Box 171)
          Catalog # WAR 417; A-side Matrix # WAR-417-A
          Wide Angle
          Minneapolis, Minnesota
        - Annie - Heartbeat; Chewing gum, 2004; SR-10698; Annie (Box 171)
          Catalog # PR 301787; A-side Matrix # ST-PR 301787 A-1
          Big Beat
        - Annie - Heartbeat (The Scrumfrog Mixes), 2005; SR-10699; Annie (Box 171)
          Catalog # PR 301966; A-side Matrix # ST-PR 301966 A-1
        - Annihilator - Do not resist the beat, 1992; SR-10700; Annihilator (Box 171)
          Catalog # N BLEED 2; A-side Matrix # N-BLEED-2-A
          Pyrotech Records
        - Anotha Level - What's that cha say, 1994; SR-10701; Anotha Level (Box 171)
          Catalog # PVL 53848; A-side Matrix # PVL-53848-A
        - Another Level - Be alone no more, 1998; SR-10702; Another Level; Jay-Z (Box 171)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # 74 324 569 36-1 A
          Northwestside Records
        - Anotha Level - Don't stimulate; What's that cha say; Fo sho shot; Doubt we ever quit, 1994; SR-10703; Anotha Level (Box 171)
          Catalog # SPRO 50805; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50805A
        - Anotha Level - On anotha level, 1994; SR-10704; Anotha Level; Ice Cube (Box 171)
          Catalog # PI 53867; A-side Matrix # PI-53867-A
        - Anotha Level - Guess I was a fool, 1998; SR-10705; Anotha Level (Box 171)
          Catalog # MAX03; A-side Matrix # MAX-03A
          Maximum Productions
        - Another Nasty Move - Two too the jaw, 1994; SR-10706; Another Nasty Move (Box 171)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # ANM-1A
          Nubian Production Enterprises, Inc
        - Another Nasty Move - Two too the jaw, 1994; SR-10707; Another Nasty Move (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10708. 2 copies
        - Another Nasty Move - Two too the jaw, 1994; SR-10708; Another Nasty Move (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10707. 2 copies
        - Anquette - Ghetto style, 1987; SR-10709; Anquette (Box 171)
          Catalog # GR-107; A-side Matrix # GR-107-A
        - Answered Questions - What you deserve, 1990; SR-10710; Answered Questions (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10711. 2 copies
          Catalog # V-56170; A-side Matrix # V-1-56170-Z2
          EMI USA
        - Answered Questions - What you deserve, 1990; SR-10711; Answered Questions (Box 171)
          In same jacket as # SR-10710. 2 copies
        - Anthony And The Camp - How many lovers, 1986; SR-10712; Anthony And The Camp (Box 171)
          Catalog # 0-20515; A-side Matrix # 0-20515-A-SHI
        - Anthony And The Camp - What I like, 1986; SR-10772; Anthony And The Camp (Box 171)
          Catalog # 0-20449; A-side Matrix # 0-20449-A-SHI
        - Anthony, Mark - Jumpin' off, 1988; SR-10773; Anthony, Mark (Box 171)
          Catalog # Z 44311; A-side Matrix # PAL 44311-1C
          Tabu Records
        - Anthony, Mark - 191 main street, 1988; SR-10774; Anthony, Mark (Box 171)
          Catalog # 4Z9 07853; A-side Matrix # XSS 07853B 1A
        - Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra - Che che colé, 2003; SR-10775; Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra; Vega, Mayra; Galindo Vega, Mayra Ernestina (Box 172)
          Catalog # DAP-12001; A-side Matrix # DAP-2001-1-A-RE
          Daptone Records
        - Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra - Che che colé, 2003; SR-10717; Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra; Vega, Mayra; Galindo Vega, Mayra Ernestina (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10718. 2 copies
        - Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra - Che che colé, 2003; SR-10718; Antibalas Afrobeat Orchestra; Vega, Mayra; Galindo Vega, Mayra Ernestina (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10717. 2 copies
        - Anton, Paul - Shake your body (Remixes), 1996; SR-10719; Anton, Paul (Box 172)
          Catalog # SIAM 12-110; A-side Matrix # SIAM 12-110 A
          Siam Records
        - Antonio - Bad funk, 1999; SR-11600; Antonio; Dub Central (Box 172)
          Catalog # LOCKED014; A-side Matrix # LOCKED 014 A-1-1-1
          Locked On
        - Anttex - Kiki Bobo, 1995; SR-10720; Anttex (Box 172)
          Catalog # STC-01; A-side Matrix # AAT13
          Jerkoff City
        - Antuan & Ray - Dance wit me, 1998; SR-10721; Antuan & Ray; Biv 10 Pee Wee All Stars (Box 172)
          Catalog # 374633055-1; A-side Matrix # 374633055-1A
          Biv 10 Records
        - Antuan & Ray Ray - Dance wit me, 1998; SR-10722; Antuan & Ray Ray; Biv 10 Pee Wee All Stars (Box 172)
          Catalog # 422860833-1; A-side Matrix # 422860833-1A/B
        - Antuan & Ray Ray - Feelin' it, 1998; SR-10723; Antuan & Ray Ray; P-Nutt; Shortee Red (Box 172)
          Catalog # U8P-1443; A-side Matrix # U8P-1443-A
        - Anu - Time for change, 1996; SR-10724; Anu; Nykee (Box 172)
          Catalog # SR1350; A-side Matrix # SR-1350-LP-A
          Simplex Records
        - Any Trouble - Touch and go; Foundations, 1983; SR-10725; Any Trouble (Box 172)
          Catalog # SPRO 9943; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9943-Z1
          EMI America
        - Anything Box - Soul on fire, 1990; SR-10726; Anything Box (Box 172)
          Catalog # 49 73541; A-side Matrix # XSS-73541B-1A
        - Anything Box - Jubilation (this thing called life), 1990; SR-10727; Anything Box (Box 172)
          Catalog # 49 73357; A-side Matrix # XSS73357B-1A G1
        - Anyzette - Baladoun, 1984; SR-10728; Anyzette (Box 172)
          Catalog # 821 480-1; A-side Matrix # 8214801 A
          Barclay
        - A.O.K. - Shack it up; The signal, 1989; SR-10729; A.O.K. (Box 172)
          Catalog # PRO-7236; A-side Matrix # PRO-7236-A-RM
          Profile Records
        - Apb - Open your eyes, 1986; SR-10730; Apb (Box 172)
          Catalog # YTHAN T 3; A-side Matrix # YTHAN T 3 A1
          Red River Records
        - Apb - One day, 1983; SR-10731; Apb (Box 172)
          Catalog # SLICK 12/10; A-side Matrix # S LICK 12_10
          Oily Records
        - Apb - What kind of girl (are you)?, 1984; SR-10732; Apb (Box 172)
          Catalog # SLX-00012; A-side Matrix # SLX-12
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Apache - Gangsta bitch; Apache ain't shit, 1992; SR-10733; Apache (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10734
          Catalog # TB 541; A-side Matrix # 1-541-A
        - Apache - Gangsta bitch; Apache ain't shit, 1992; SR-10734; Apache (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10733
        - Apache Indian - Chok there, 1993; SR-10735; Apache Indian; Raja, Don (Box 172)
          Catalog # 162-537 875; A-side Matrix # 162537 857-1 ASHS
        - Apache Indian - Armagideon time, 1995; SR-10736; Apache Indian (Box 172)
          Catalog # PR12 7049-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 7049-1A
        - Apache Indian - No reservations, 1993; SR-10737; Apache Indian (Box 172)
          Catalog # 162-539 932; A-side Matrix # 162-539 032-1-AS/HS
        - Apani - Abracadabra; Say what?!?!, 2003; SR-10738; Apani (Box 172)
          Catalog # QB002; A-side Matrix # QB-002A
          Q-Boro Sounds
        - Aphillyation - Dry tears; To this…, 1998; SR-10739; Aphillyation (Box 172)
          Catalog # TB 485; A-side Matrix # TB-485-A
        - Aphrodelics - Trailers EP, 1998; SR-10740; Aphrodelics (Box 172)
          Catalog # UPTIGHT 24; A-side Matrix # APHRODELICS-A2
          Uptight
          Vienna, Austria
        - Aphrodite - Recuts 1, 1996; SR-10741; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          Catalog # APH RECUTS1; A-side Matrix # APHROCUT1 A1
          Aphrodite Recordings
        - Aphrodite - Recuts 7, 2001; SR-10742; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          Catalog # ADN4; A-side Matrix # AND 004 A2
        - Aphrodite - See thru it, 2002; SR-10743; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          Catalog # VVR5020986; A-side Matrix # VVR 5020986 A-1-1
          V2
        - Aphrodite - Aphrodite Recordings (Disc One), 1999; SR-10744; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10745; SR-10746; SR-10747; SR-10748; SR-10749. Multi-disc album
          Catalog # VVR1006951; A-side Matrix # VVR 1006951
        - Aphrodite - Aphrodite Recordings (Disc Two), 1999; SR-10745; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10744; SR-10746; SR-10747; SR-10748; SR-10749. Multi-disc album
        - Aphrodite - Aphrodite Recordings (Disc Three), 1999; SR-10746; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10744; SR-10745; SR-10747; SR-10748; SR-10749. Multi-disc album
        - Aphrodite - Aphrodite Recordings (Disc Four), 1999; SR-10747; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10744; SR-10745; SR-10746; SR-10748; SR-10749. Multi-disc album
        - Aphrodite - Aphrodite Recordings (Disc Five), 1999; SR-10748; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10744; SR-10745; SR-10746; SR-10747; SR-10749. Multi-disc album
        - Aphrodite - Aphrodite Recordings (Disc Six), 1999; SR-10749; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10744; SR-10745; SR-10746; SR-10747; SR-10748. Multi-disc album
        - Aphrodite - BM funkster; Cross channel, 2000; SR-10750; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          Catalog # APH34; A-side Matrix # APH 34 A1
        - Aphrodite - All over me, 2002; SR-10751; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          Catalog # VVR5018886; A-side Matrix # VVR 5018886A-1-1
        - Aphrodite - Woman that rolls EP, 1999; SR-10752; Aphrodite (Box 172)
          Catalog # GVWH-33586; A-side Matrix # 6322-33586-1-A
        - Aphrodite - The takeover bid (Disc One), 1998; SR-10753; Aphrodite; Finn, Mickey (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10754; SR-10755. Triple album
          Catalog # MMLLP025; A-side Matrix # MMLLP025-A1
          Mixmag
          Slough, United Kingdom
        - Aphrodite - The takeover bid (Disc Two), 1998; SR-10754; Aphrodite; Finn, Mickey (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10753; SR-10755. Triple album
          Catalog # MMLLP025; A-side Matrix # MMLLP025-C1
        - Aphrodite - The takeover bid (Disc Three), 1998; SR-10755; Aphrodite; Finn, Mickey (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10753; SR-10754. Triple album
          Catalog # MMLLP025; A-side Matrix # MMLLP025-E1
        - Apocolypse - Sex you; Skills prevail, 1996; SR-10756; Apocolypse (Box 172)
          Catalog # VNoo1; A-side Matrix # VN-001-SEX SIDE
          Venom Records
        - Apollo - Apollo, 1979; SR-10757; Apollo (Box 172)
          Catalog # GZ-985R1; A-side Matrix # GZ-985R1A
          Gordy
        - Apollonia 6 - Blue limousine, 1984; SR-10758; Apollonia 6 (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10759. 2 copies
          Catalog # W 9092; A-side Matrix # W9092
        - Apollonia 6 - Blue limousine, 1984; SR-10759; Apollonia 6 (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10758. 2 copies
        - Apollonia 6 - Blue limousine, 1984; SR-10760; Apollonia 6 (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10761. 2 copies
        - Apollonia 6 - Blue limousine, 1984; SR-10761; Apollonia 6 (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10760. 2 copies
        - Apollonia 6 - Apollonia 6, 1984; SR-10762; Apollonia 6 (Box 172)
          Catalog # 25108-1; A-side Matrix # 25108-1A
          Australia & New Zealand
        - Apollonia 6 - Since I fell for you, 1988; SR-10763; Apollonia 6 (Box 172)
          Catalog # PRO-A-3291; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-3291-SH
        - Apollofourfourty - Krupa, 1996; SR-10764; Apollofourfourty (Box 172)
          Catalog # SSR5 THREE; A-side Matrix # SSR-5-THREE-A2
          Stealth Sonic Records
        - Apollofourfourty - Stop the rock, 1999; SR-10765; Apollofourfourty (Box 172)
          Catalog # BAS 47450; A-side Matrix # XSS-47450-A
          550 Music
        - Appell, Ian - Vacuum; Truckin', 1997; SR-10766; Appell, Ian (Box 172)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # HAL 12788-A
          Afrowax Records
          South Beach, Florida
        - April - Special love, 1987; SR-10767; April (Box 172)
          Catalog # JJJ-001; A-side Matrix # JJJ001-A
          Triple J Records
        - Aqua Bassino - We could be friends, 2003; SR-10768; Aqua Bassino; Smith, Tracy (Box 172)
          Catalog # F172W; A-side Matrix # B268234-01A1
        - Aqua Bassino - Beat's n bobs (Disc One), 2001; SR-10769; Aqua Bassino (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10770. Double album
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # B147819-01 A1
        - Aqua Bassino - Beat's n bobs (Disc Two), 2001; SR-10770; Aqua Bassino (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10769. Double album
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # B147819-02 C1
        - Aqua Bassino - Baby c'mon remixes, 2002; SR-10771; Aqua Bassino (Box 172)
          Catalog # F 158; A-side Matrix # B158047-01A1
        - Aqua People - I like it wet, 1983; SR-10776; Aqua People (Box 172)
          Catalog # SP-1000; A-side Matrix # AP-611-V
          Spido Records
        - Aqua Regia - N.Y.C. smile on me (The DFC remix), 1990; SR-10777; Aqua Regia (Box 172)
          Catalog # DFC 021; A-side Matrix # DFC 021 A
        - Aqua Regia - Rugelach, 1990; SR-10778; Aqua Regia (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10779. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # HB 90019; A-side Matrix # HB90019A 1-1
          Hillbilly House Records
        - Aqua Regia - Rugelach, 1990; SR-10779; Aqua Regia (Box 172)
          In same jacket as # SR-10778. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Arbeid Adelt ? - Disco death, 1987; SR-10781; Arbeid Adelt ?; Arbeid Adelt (Box 173)
          Catalog # BAA 1; A-side Matrix # BAA 1-A // 61057-1
          Play It Again Sam
          Brussels, Belgium
        - Arcade Funk - Search and destroy, 1983; SR-10782; Arcade Funk (Box 173)
          Catalog # DT 001; A-side Matrix # TD 002 A
          D.E.T.T. Records
          Landover, Maryland
        - Arcadia - Election day (the consensus mix), 1985; SR-10783; Arcadia (Box 173)
          Catalog # V-15209; A-side Matrix # V-1-15209-X601075B-Z1
        - Archie - We ready, 2002; SR-10784; Archie; Archie Eversole; Bubba Sparxxx (Box 173)
          Catalog # MCAR-25745-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR 257451-A
        - Archies - Sugar, Sugar (Special Extended Candyfloss Mix), 1987; SR-10785; Archies (Box 173)
          Catalog # DEBTX 3030; A-side Matrix # DEBTX-3030-A1
          Debut
        - Archies - Straight A's, 1981; SR-10786; Archies (Box 173)
          Catalog # SN-7149; A-side Matrix # SN-1-7149
          Accord
        - Architechs - Show me the money, 2001; SR-10787; Architechs (Box 173)
          Catalog # SHOW 2; A-side Matrix # SHOW-2-A
          Go! Beat
        - Architechs - Body groove, 2000; SR-10788; Architechs (Box 173)
          Catalog # NANA12PRO; A-side Matrix # NANA-12-PRO-A
        - Architechs - Music 2 write 2 (Disc one), 2003; SR-10789; Architechs (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10790; SR-10791; SR-10792. Double album; 2 copies
          Catalog # PLE7016; A-side Matrix # PLE-7016A
          Pockets Linted Entertainment
          Brisbane, California
        - Architechs - Music 2 write 2 (Disc two), 2003; SR-10790; Architechs (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10789; SR-10791; SR-10792. Double album; 2 copies
          Catalog # PLE7016; A-side Matrix # PLE-7016C
        - Architechs - Music 2 write 2 (Disc one), 2003; SR-10791; Architechs (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10789; SR-10790; SR-10792. Double album; 2 copies
        - Architechs - Music 2 write 2 (Disc two), 2003; SR-10792; Architechs (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10789; SR-10790; SR-10791. Double album; 2 copies